<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<code-table>
    <code-table-name>document-type-code</code-table-name>
    <items>
        <item>
            <hint>
                <p>Every time you click a tab (including the current one), your input is saved. </p>
                <p>When you click "Finish Editing", your input is saved, and you return to the search interface where your record is displayed. </p>
                <p>The record is saved inside the folder you marked before opening the editor or the folder from which you opened it for re-editing.</p>
                <p>Be aware that you are only logged in for 30 minutes and that when your session times out, you will be returned to the search interface and what you have input without saving it cannot be retrieved.</p>
                <p>You can keep your session alive for another 30 minutes by clicking any tab. When your session is about to expire, you are prompted to keep it alive and given 5 minutes to react.</p>
                <p>If you know that you may not be able to finish a record, it is best to click "Finish Editing" and return later to continue editing it.</p>
                <p>You can continue editing the record by finding it and clicking the "Edit Record" button inside the record's detail view.</p>
                <p>If you wish to discard your edits, click "Cancel Editing" at the bottom of the page. None of the edits you have made will then be saved and you will be shown the original record again.</p>
            </hint>
            <value>save</value>
        </item>
        <item>
            <label>(none selected)</label>
            <value/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <label>Periodical</label>
            <value>periodical</value>
            <classifier>stand-alone</classifier>
            <sort>1</sort>
        </item>
        <item>
            <label>Edited Volume</label>
            <value>edited-volume</value>
            <classifier>stand-alone</classifier>
            <sort>1</sort>
        </item>
        <item>
            <label>Article in Periodical</label>
            <value>article-in-periodical</value>
            <classifier>stand-alone</classifier>
            <sort>1</sort>
            <hint>
                <p>For an <strong>Article in Periodical</strong>, on the <strong>Article</strong> tab, one would normally input the following
                    information:</p>
                <p>Input the name(s) of the author(s) in <strong>Names and Roles</strong>, leaving "author" selected as Role. Divide the name into Given Name and
                    Family Name, if possible.</p>
                <p>Input the title of the article in <strong>Title Information</strong>, dividing this into Title and Subtitle, if possible. If the title begins
                    with an article like "A" or "The," remove this from the title and input it in Non Sort.</p>
                <p>In case the publication is (also) electronic, input in <strong>URL</strong> the web address of the publication.</p>
                <p>Finally, in <strong>Identifier</strong> input the DOI number of the article, if available.</p>
                <p>&#160;</p>
                <p>Use the <strong>Periodical</strong> tab to catalogue the periodical that the article occurs in and the position of the article inside the
                    periodical.</p>
                <p>Input the title of the periodical in <strong>Periodical Title</strong>. Follow the same guidelines that apply to book titles.</p>
                <p>Input the name(s) of the editor(s) of the periodical in <strong>Names and Roles</strong>. Choose "personal," "corporate" or "conference" as
                    Type of Name as applies to the periodical in question. If the "editor" is personal, select "Given Name" and "Family Name" instead of "(none
                    selected)."</p>
                <p>In <strong>Location of Article in Periodical</strong> note the volume number, issue number and year of publication of the periodical in which
                    the article has appeared. Enter the page numbers of the article in the volume and/or issue it occurs in.</p>
                <p>Finally, in <strong>Identifier</strong> input the ISSN number of the periodical and its DOI, if available.</p>
            </hint>
        </item>
        <item>
            <label>Article in Periodical</label>
            <value>related-article-in-periodical</value>
            <classifier>related-item</classifier>
            <sort>1</sort>
        </item>
        <item>
            <label>Book Review</label>
            <value>related-book-review-in-periodical</value>
            <classifier>related-item</classifier>
            <sort>1</sort>
        </item>
        <!--<item>
            <label>Book Chapter</label>
            <value>related-monograph-chapter</value>
            <classifier>related-item</classifier>
            <sort>1</sort>
        </item>-->
        <item>
            <label>Contribution to Edited Volume</label>
            <value>related-contribution-to-edited-volume</value>
            <classifier>related-item</classifier>
            <sort>1</sort>
        </item>
        <item>
            <label>Contribution to Edited Volume</label>
            <value>contribution-to-edited-volume</value>
            <classifier>stand-alone</classifier>
            <sort>1</sort>
        </item>
        <item>
            <label>Book</label>
            <value>monograph</value>
            <classifier>stand-alone</classifier>
            <hint>
                <p>For a <strong>Book</strong>, on the <strong>Book</strong> tab, one would normally input the following information:</p>
                <p>Input the name(s) of the author(s) in <strong>Names and Roles</strong>, selecting "author" as Role. Divide the name into Given Name and
                    Family Name, if possible.</p>
                <p>If there is more than one author, repeat the <strong>Names and Roles</strong> fields by clicking the '+' button.</p>
                <p>Input the title of the book in <strong>Title Information</strong>, dividing this into Title and Subtitle, if possible. If the title
                    begins with an article like the English "A" or "The", remove this from the title and input it in Non Sort.</p>
                <p>In <strong>Origin Information</strong>, input the city in which the publisher resides and the name of the publisher. If more than one of
                    these is in evidence, input the main one or the first of them. Finally, input the year the book was issued or copyrighted. </p>
                <p>In <strong>Physical Description</strong>, input the extent of the book in pages, e.g. "ix, 214 p."</p>
                <p>In case the book is (also) electronic, input in <strong>URL</strong> the web address of the book.</p>
                <p>Finally, in <strong>Identifier</strong> input the ISBN number of the book, preferably a 13-digit ISBN, and a DOI, if available.</p>
                <p>&#160;</p>
                <p>Use the <strong>Book Series</strong> tab only if the book is part of a series.</p>
                <p>Input the title of the series in <strong>Series Title</strong>. Follow the same guidelines that apply to book titles.</p>
                <p>Input the name(s) of the editor(s) of the series in <strong>Names and Roles</strong>. Choose "personal," "corporate" or "conference" as Type
                    of Name as applies to the book in question. If the "editor" is not personal, select "(none selected)" instead of "Given Name" and
                    "Family Name."</p>
                <p>In <strong>Location of Book in Series</strong> note the volume number of the book within the series.</p>
                <p>In <strong>Identifier</strong> input the ISSN number of the book series and a DOI, if available.</p>
            </hint>
            <sort>1</sort>
        </item>
        <item>
            <label>Book Review</label>
            <value>book-review</value>
            <classifier>stand-alone</classifier>
            <sort>1</sort>
        </item>
        <item>
            <label>SUEBS Tibetan</label>
            <value>suebs-tibetan</value>
            <classifier>stand-alone</classifier>
            <sort>1</sort>
        </item>
        <!-- hard-coded tabs.xqm, line 22. -->
        <item>
            <label>Almost Full MODS 3.4 Schema</label>
            <value>insert-templates</value>
            <classifier>stand-alone</classifier>
            <sort>2</sort>
        </item>
        <item>
            <label>Fairly Full MODS 3.4 Schema</label>
            <value>new-instance</value>
            <classifier>stand-alone</classifier>
            <sort>2</sort>
        </item>
        <!--<item>
            <label>MADS record</label>
            <value>mads</value>
            <classifier>stand-alone</classifier>
            <sort>3</sort>
        </item>-->
    </items>
</code-table>