<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--let $code-table :=
--><!--let $code-table :=
-->
<code-table>
    <code-table-name>hint-code</code-table-name>
    <items>
        <item>
            <help/>
            <hint>Click to add another frame with the same contents after the frame with the blue background.</hint>
            <value>add-frame</value>
            <local-name/>
            <tab-id/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <help>
                <p>The Type field can take the following values: personal, corporate, conference. Use it to indicate whether the name is the name of a person
                    (or a family), the name of a corporation or the name of a conference (or an event similar to a conference).</p>
            </help>
            <hint> Type identifies what type of Title Information is recorded, if this information is special. If the title is recorded as it appears on the
                title page, it does not have Type and Type should be left empty. Use a value for Type if the title is abbreviated, translated, alternative, or
                uniform (a transliteration is here regarded as a form of translation). </hint>
            <value>name-type</value>
            <local-name/>
            <tab-id>type</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item>
            <help/>
            <hint>Click to remove the frame with blue background.</hint>
            <value>remove-frame</value>
            <local-name/>
            <tab-id/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <help>
                <p> Enter here information related to the edited volume that the edited volume contribution you are cataloguing occurs in. This information
                    falls into two groups: general information on the edited volume and specific information on the location of the edited volume contribution
                    in the edited volume.</p>
            </help>
            <value>edited-volume-compact</value>
            <local-name/>
            <tab-id/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <help>
                <p> Abstract is used to record a succinct summary of some aspect of the content of the resource. </p>
                <p> More input options can be accessed by clicking the Subjects tab on Context Description Forms.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>abstract</value>
            <local-name>abstract</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <help>
                <p>Affiliation contains the name, address, etc. of an organisation with which the person in Name was associated when the resource was created.</p>
                <p>If the information is readily available, it may be included.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>affiliation</value>
            <local-name>affiliation</local-name>
            <parent>name</parent>
            <tab-id/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <help>
                <p>Alternate Representation Groups is used to link alternate representations of the same element content, such as different scripts,
                    transliterations, and translations. The same attribute value is applied to each of the element instances to be linked.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>altRepGroup</value>
            <local-name>altRepGroup</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <help>
                <p> The name of the authoritative list for an abbreviated title is recorded here. </p>
            </help>
            <hint> The name of the authoritative list for an abbreviated title is recorded here. </hint>
            <value>abbreviated-title-authority</value>
            <local-name>authority</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <help>
                <p> The name of an authoritative list for a controlled value in Name is recorded here. </p>
                <p> If you render the name as it occurs in the resource, you may leave the Authority field value blank. If you normalize the name, you should
                    indicate according to which authority you are altering it. Use the value "Local" if a locally-developed name authority file is used to
                    catalogue the Name in question. </p>
            </help>
            <hint> Type identifies what type of Title Information is recorded, if this information is special. If the title is recorded as it appears on the
                title page, it does not have Type and Type should be left empty. Use a value for Type if the title is abbreviated, translated, alternative, or
                uniform (a transliteration is here regarded as a form of translation). </hint>
            <value>name-authority</value>
            <local-name>authority</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <help>
                <p> The name of an authoritative list for a controlled value in Name is recorded here. </p>
                <p> If you render the name as it occurs in the resource, you may leave the Authority field value blank. If you normalize the name, you should
                    indicate according to which authority you are altering it. Use the value "Local" if a locally-developed name authority file is used to
                    catalogue the Name in question. </p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>namePart-authority</value>
            <local-name>authority</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <help>
                <p> The name of the authoritative list for a uniform title is recorded here. </p>
            </help>
            <hint> The name of the authoritative list for a uniform title is recorded here. </hint>
            <value>uniform-title-authority</value>
            <local-name>authority</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <help/>
            <hint/>
            <value>name-authority-uri</value>
            <local-name>authorityUri</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <help/>
            <hint/>
            <value>titleInfo-authorityURI</value>
            <local-name>authorityURI</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <help>
                <p> Note in Year of Publication the year in which the resource was published, released, or issued. </p>
                <p> Use Point if you wish to record a span of time, e.g. 1912-1914. The values "start" and "end" are used with Point. Repeat the Year of
                    Publication field and choose "start" in one and "end" in the other repetition, and enter the appropriate dates in the two Year of
                    Publication fields. </p>
                <p> If no point is specified a year noted in Year of Publication is assumed to be a single year. </p>
                <p> More input options can be found on the Origin Info tab on the Citation Forms.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>dateIssued-compact</value>
            <local-name>dateIssued</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <help>
                <p>Description contains a textual description for a name when this is necessary, for example, to distinguish it from other names.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>description</value>
            <local-name>description</local-name>
            <parent>name</parent>
            <tab-id/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <help>
                <p>The Display Form field makes it possible to display personal names in unstructured form. It typically renders a name as given on the
                    resource. </p>
                <p> For some applications, contractual agreements require that the form of the name provided on the resource be provided.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>name-displayForm</value>
            <local-name>displayForm</local-name>
            <parent>name</parent>
            <tab-id/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <help>
                <p>
                    <p>This field is used when additional text associated with the name is needed for display. Display Label may be used whenever appropriate to
                        indicate the preferred labeling when displayed. Include the text and capitalization preferred, but do not include delimiters such as
                        colons or semicolons.</p>
                </p>
            </help>
            <hint>Display Label is used when additional text associated with the title is needed for display. </hint>
            <value>name-displayLabel</value>
            <local-name>displayLabel</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <help>
                <p> Display Label is used when additional text associated with the title is needed for display. Display Label may be used whenever appropriate
                    to indicate the preferred labeling when displayed. Appropriate cases include titles other than the primary title or subtitle. Include the
                    text preferred and capitalisation, but do not include delimiters such as colons. </p>
            </help>
            <hint>Display Label is used when additional text associated with the title is needed for display. </hint>
            <value>titleInfo-displayLabel</value>
            <local-name>displayLabel</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <help>
                <p> Encoding is used to note the encoding followed in the date notation. The recommendation is to use the w3cdtf encoding. According to this
                    encoding, dates are formatted in the following way: Year: YYYY (eg 1997); Year and month: YYYY-MM (eg 1997-07); Complete date: YYYY-MM-DD
                    (eg 1997-07-16). If you are inputting a controlled subject term such as the designation of a period or an era, leave this field blank. </p>
            </help>
            <value>temporal-encoding</value>
            <local-name>encoding</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <help>
                <p> A statement of the number and specific material of the units of the resource that express physical extent. A typical entry for a book might
                    read "xiv, 213 p."</p>
                <p> Extent may be used with electronic resources, e.g. digitised collection of slides, to show how many slides constitute the resource. </p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>extent-compact</value>
            <local-name>extent</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <help>
                <p>Use here standard names for geographical places.</p>
                <p>Add as many Place fields as you need.</p>
                <p>The relation between the different fields is not specified, but one may start with more abstract terms and move to more specific terms,
                    within the same Subject.</p>
                <p> More input options can be accessed by clicking the Subjects tab on Context Description Forms.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>geographic</value>
            <local-name>geographic</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <help>
                <p> ID is used to link among records inside the database and to reference a field inside the database from outside the database. </p>
            </help>
            <hint> ID is used to link among records inside the database and to reference a field inside the database from outside the database. </hint>
            <value>ID</value>
            <local-name>ID</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <help>
                <p>Enter here primarily the International Standard Book Number (ISBN) number of the book you are cataloguing or its Digital Object Identifier
                    (DOI). </p>
                <p>Use the 13-digit version of the ISBN number, if available.</p>
                <p>If you have access to another unique identifier, please record it.</p>
            </help>
            <value>isbn</value>
            <local-name>identifier</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <help>
                <p>Enter here primarily the International Standard Serial Number (ISSN) number of the periodical you are cataloguing and/or its Digital Object
                    Identifier (DOI). </p>
                <p>If you have access to any other unique identifier, please record it.</p>
            </help>
            <value>identifier-periodical-compact</value>
            <local-name>identifier</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <help>
                <p> Use this field if the resource is electronic. An identification of the electronic format type, or the data representation of the resource.
                    Internet Media Type specifies the electronic format type of the resource, such as text/html, PDF file, JPEG image or executable application
                    .</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>internetMediaType-compact</value>
            <local-name>internetMediaType</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <help>
                <p> The language used within the input field is specified here, if this language is different from the language noted in Language of Resource.
                    The most common languages have been moved to the top of the list. </p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>lang</value>
            <local-name>lang</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <help>
                <p> The language used within Title Information is specified here. The most common languages have been moved to the top of the list. </p>
                <p>The language noted here is the language chosen when the record was created. It applies to the record as a whole, unless otherwise noted.
                    Since a title or a name as a subject can be in any language, the Global Language can be overruled here by chosing a Local Language.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>lang-global-compact</value>
            <local-name>lang</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <help>
                <p> The language used within Title Information is specified here. The most common languages have been moved to the top of the list. </p>
                <p>The language noted here is not the language chosen when the record was created. The language noted here only applies to the field(s)
                    immediately below. Since a title or a name as a subject can be in any language , the Global Language can be overruled here by chosing a
                    Local Language.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>lang-local-compact</value>
            <local-name>lang</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <help>
                <p> The language used within Name Information is specified here, if this language is different from the language noted in Language of Resource.
                    The most common languages have been moved to the top of the list. </p>
                <p> Language can be applied the Name as a whole. Do this if you are using only one Language value for all Name Parts. If you are using different
                    values for different Name Parts, apply Language to each Name Part and leave Language empty under Name as a whole. </p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>name-lang</value>
            <local-name>lang</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <help>
                <p>The language used within Title Information is specified here, if this language is different from the language noted in Language of Resource.
                    The most common languages have been moved to the top of the list. </p>
                <p> Language can be applied the Name as a whole. Do this if you are using only one Language value for all Name Parts. If you are using different
                    values for different Name Parts, apply Language to each Name Part and leave Language empty under Name as a whole. </p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>namePart-lang</value>
            <local-name>lang</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <help>
                <p> In Names are catalogued the names of the persons, organisations, or events (conferences, meetings, etc.) that are associated with the
                    resource being catalogued. These relationship between these named entities and the resource is described in Role. </p>
                <p>Include as many Names blocks as needed. </p>
                <p> In addition to describing named entities associated with the creation of a resource, Names is also used as a kind of Subject. For names used
                    as subjects, to note that the resource is about a named entity, see the Subjects tab. </p>
                <p> For textual materials, include the names of all known authors, translators, compilers, and editors. </p>
                <p> For images, include the name of the creator of the original intellectual content (the original photographer, painter, architect, etc.) and
                    the name of anyone capturing that content in a new medium (for a photograph of a building, include both the architect and the photographer). </p>
                <p> If no known person or organisation etc. is known to be associated with the resource, or if the person or organisation etc. is anonymous, do
                    not use "unknown," "anonymous," or similar annotations; rather, leave the Names block empty. </p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>name</value>
            <local-name>name</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <help>
                <p> In Names and Roles, catalogue the names of each person, corporation or conference associated with the resource.</p>
                <p> Include as many Names and Roles as needed, by clicking the '+' button. </p>
                <p> Choose an appropriate Type of Name for each name, "personal" for personal names, "corporate" for names of institutions, and "conference" for
                    names of events such as conferences..</p>
                <p> Please notice that the role pertaining to a name follows the name in question.</p>
                <p> More input options can be found on the Name Info tab on the Citation Forms.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>name-relatedItem-periodical-editor-compact</value>
            <local-name>name</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <help>
                <p> In Names and Roles, catalogue the names of each person, corporation or conference associated with the resource.</p>
                <p> Include as many Names and Roles as needed, by clicking the '+' button. </p>
                <p> Choose an appropriate Type of Name for each name, "personal" for personal names, "corporate" for names of institutions, and "conference" for
                    names of events such as conferences. If you choose "corporate" or "conference," please clear the values "Given" and "Family" in front of the
                    name parts by choosing "(none selected)." Conversely, if you add a personal name, please choose "Given Name" and "Family Name" as is
                    relevant. </p>
                <p> Given Name and Family Name can occur in any order. </p>
                <p> Please notice that the role pertaining to a name follows the name in question. </p>
                <p> More input options can be found on the Name Information tab on the Citation Forms.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>name-compact</value>
            <local-name>name</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <help>
                <p> In Persons and Institutions as Topics, catalogue the names of each person or institution that serves as topic of the resource you are
                    calaloguing. </p>
                <p>Add as many Persons and Institutions as Topics as is necessary. Click on "P+" to add a personal name and on "I+" to add the name of an
                    institution.</p>
                <p> More input options can be accessed by clicking the Subjects tab on Context Description Forms.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>subject-name</value>
            <local-name>name</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <help>
                <p> Analyse each name into separate name parts, e.g. Given Name and Family Name.</p>
                <p> If this is not possible, choose "(none selected)" and enter the whole name in the field in question.</p>
                <p> If a given or family name consists of several parts, enter all parts of the same type in the same field.</p>
                <p> More input options can be accessed by clicking the Subjects tab on Context Description Forms.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>subject-name-corporate</value>
            <local-name>name</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <help>
                <p> Analyse each name into separate name parts, e.g. Given Name and Family Name.</p>
                <p> If this is not possible, choose "(none selected)" and enter the whole name in the field in question.</p>
                <p> If a given or family name consists of several parts, enter all parts of the same type in the same field.</p>
                <p> More input options can be accessed by clicking the Subjects tab on Context Description Forms.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>subject-name-personal</value>
            <local-name>name</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <help>
                <p> In Names and Roles, catalogue the names of each person, corporation or conference associated with the resource.</p>
                <p> Include as many Names and Roles as needed, by clicking the '+' button. </p>
                <p> Choose an appropriate Type of Name for each name, "personal" for personal names, "corporate" for names of institutions, and "conference" for
                    names of events such as conferences..</p>
                <p> Please notice that the role pertaining to a name follows the name in question.</p>
                <p> More input options can be found on the Name Information tab on the Citation Forms.</p>
            </help>
            <value>edited-volume-name-compact</value>
            <local-name>name</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <help>
                <p>The name itself is always entered into a Name Part. This is the case even if it is not possible to parse the name into separate units.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>namePart</value>
            <local-name>namePart</local-name>
            <parent>name</parent>
            <tab-id/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <help>
                <p> Analyse each name into separate name parts, i.e. Given Name and Family Name.</p>
                <p> If possible, analyse each personal name into Given Name and Family Name. If this is not possible, choose "(none selected)" and enter the
                    whole name in the field in question.</p>
                <p> If a given or family name consists of several parts, enter all parts of the same type in the same field.</p>
                <p> If the name is in a language that is usually transliterated, enter the transliterated name parts in their respective fields. Use the
                    transliteration scheme you chose when selecting a record template. </p>
                <p> More input options can be found on the Name Information tab on the Citation Forms.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>namePart-compact</value>
            <local-name>namePart</local-name>
            <parent>name</parent>
            <tab-id/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <help>
                <p> Analyse each corporate name into separate name parts. Record the more general designation in the first field and a more specific designation
                    in the second field. If this is not possible, enter the whole name in one field.</p>
                <p> If the name is in a language that is usually transliterated, enter the transliterated name parts in their respective fields. Use the
                    transliteration scheme you chose when selecting a record template. </p>
                <p> More input options can be found on the Name Information tab on the Citation Forms.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>namePart-institution-compact</value>
            <local-name>namePart</local-name>
            <parent>name</parent>
            <tab-id/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <help>
                <p>Name Part includes each part of the name. Parsing is used to parse parts of a personal name into family/surname and given name/forename, as
                    well as terms of address, but it is also used to indicate a date associated with the name and to parse the parts of a corporate name. </p>
                <p> The parsing performed is indicated by the Type field. This field takes the following values: Date, Family, Given, Terms Of Address. </p>
                <p> Date is used to note dates that are not integral parts of a name. For dates within e.g. a conference name, do not use this field to separate
                    the date, since it is an integral part of the name of the conference. The birthdate associated with a personal name, however, is not an
                    integral part of the name, but can be added to distinguish the name from others, so it does include a separate Name Part with a Type of
                    "Date". </p>
                <p> "Family" is used for the family name or surname of a person. </p>
                <p> "Given" is used for the given name or forename of a person. </p>
                <p> "Terms Of Address" is used to record titles and enumeration associated with a name, such as "Jr.", "II", etc. </p>
                <p> If you do not know how to break up a name or if a name is not constructed according to the family name/given name pattern, leave the Type of
                    the Name Part blank and enter the whole name as it occurs. </p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>namePart-type</value>
            <local-name>namePart</local-name>
            <parent>name</parent>
            <tab-id/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <help>
                <p> Name-Title Group that can be used with Name and Title Information to enable an explicit link between a name and a title when that is
                    desirable. The same value is assigned to this attribute for the two elements. This attribute is used to link names to uniform titles when
                    the name-uniform title combination is an authority controlled heading. </p>
            </help>
            <hint>Name-Title Group that can be used with Name and Title Information to enable an explicit link between a name and a title when that is
                desirable. The same value is assigned to this attribute for the two elements.</hint>
            <value>nameTitleGroup</value>
            <local-name>nameTitleGroup</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <help>
                <p> Non Sort contains characters, including initial articles (typically "A" and "The" in English), punctuation, and spaces that appear at the
                    beginning of a title that should be ignored when indexing and sorting. </p>
                <p> Non Sort should only be used with languages that have preposed articles. </p>
            </help>
            <hint>Non Sort contains words that appear at the beginning of a title which should be ignored when indexing and sorting. Examples are "A" and "The"
                in English.</hint>
            <value>nonSort</value>
            <local-name>nonSort</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <help>
                <p> General information relating to a resource. </p>
                <p> Note should be used only for information that cannot be encoded in another, more specific, ways. </p>
                <p> More input options can be accessed by clicking the Subjects tab on Context Description Forms.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>note</value>
            <local-name>note</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <help>
                <p> Enter here information about the publication's origin, including its place of origin or publication, its publisher, and its date of issue or
                    date of copyright. </p>
                <p> More input options can be found on the Origin Info tab on the Citation Forms.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>originInfo-compact</value>
            <local-name>originInfo</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <help>
                <p> Note here in which volume and issue the article you are cataloguing occurs in the periodical, in which year the volume/issue was published,
                    and on which pages the article occurs.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>part-relatedItem-periodical-compact</value>
            <local-name>part</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <help>
                <p> Part Name is used for a part or section name of a title. Use Part Name when a part name is present, rather than including the part name in
                    the text of Title. Use Part Name to describe the section or division titles of a digital object (for example, a chapter title, episode name,
                    or an audio or video clip). </p>
                <p> If a resource has multiple parts, each with its own Part Name, the work should be catalogued in as many records as there are Part Names.
                    <!--NB: not implemented: Multiple Part Name fields may be nested in a single Title Information to describe a single part with multiple hierarchical levels; multiple parts, however, should be separated into multiple Title Information blocks. -->
                </p>
                <p> When representing the Part Name, do not include punctuation at the end of the preceding field intended to separate the part name from
                    previous parts of the title. <!--Multiple parts of an item should appear in separate records or as Related Items.-->
                </p>
            </help>
            <hint>Part Name is used for the name of a part of a resource. If a book has "Part One" as its Part Number, it could have "The First Years" as its
                Part Name. If a resource has multiple parts, each with its own Part Name, the work should be catalogued in as many records as there are Part
                Names.</hint>
            <value>partName</value>
            <local-name>partName</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <help>
                <p> Part Number is used for a part or section number in a title. </p>
                <p> Use Part Number when a part number is present, rather than including the part number in the text of the Title. </p>
                <p> A Part Number does not have to be a digit, i.e. "First Part" may be the contents of the Part Number field if this is how it occurs on the
                    title page. </p>
                <p> Part Number may describe the section of an digital object (for example, an episode number or an audio or video clip). </p>
                <p> When using Part Number, do not include punctuation at the end of the preceding field intended to separate the part number from previous
                    parts of the title. </p>
            </help>
            <hint> Part Number is used for a part or section number in a title. A Part Number does not have to be a digit, i.e. "Part One" may be Part Number. </hint>
            <value>partNumber</value>
            <local-name>partNumber</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <help>
                <p> In this compact input format, only the Internet Media Type and the Extent of the publication are noted in Physical Description.</p>
                <p> More input options can be found on the Physical Description tab on the Citation Forms.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>physicalDescription-compact</value>
            <local-name>physicalDescription</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <help>
                <p> Record in City Name the city in which the publisher has its principal domicile, as noted on the title page. </p>
                <p> If the publisher is housed in several cities, record the one given prominence on the title page. If all are given equal prominence, record
                    the first city name.</p>
                <p> If the city name is in a language that is usually transliterated, enter the transliterated city name in its field. Use the transliteration
                    scheme you chose when selecting a record template.</p>
                <p> More input options can be found on the Origin Info tab on the Citation Forms.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>place-compact</value>
            <local-name>place</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <help>
                <p>Point is used to note whether the date noted is a start point or an end point. If no point is specified, date is assumed to be a single date.
                </p>
            </help>
            <value>temporal-point</value>
            <local-name>point</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <help>
                <p> Record in Publisher Name the name of the entity that is the originator for a resource, i.e. that has published, printed, distributed,
                    released, issued, or produced it, as noted on the title page. </p>
                <p> If the publisher name is in a language that is usually transliterated, enter the transliterated publisher name in its field. Use the
                    transliteration scheme you chose when selecting a record template. </p>
                <p> More input options can be found on the Origin Info tab of the Citation Forms.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>publisher-compact</value>
            <local-name>publisher</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <help>
                <p> Enter here information related to the periodical that the article you are cataloguing occurs in. This information falls into two groups:
                    general information on the periodical and specific information on the location of the article in the periodical.</p>
            </help>
            <value>relatedItem-periodical-compact</value>
            <local-name>relatedItem</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <help>
                <p> Enter here the title of the periodical you are cataloguing. If the title divides into a main title and a subtitle, enter each part in its
                    separate field. </p>
                <p> If the title is in a language that is usually transliterated, enter the transliterated title and subtitle in their respective fields. Use
                    the transliteration scheme you chose when selecting a record template. </p>
                <p> If you believe it is useful to supply a translation of the title, do so in their relevant fields. Note the language that the title
                    information is translated into (the default is English). </p>
                <p> The language used is only specified if it is different from the language noted in Language of Resource when you selected the record
                    template. The most common languages have been moved to the top of the list. </p>
            </help>
            <value>relatedItem-periodical-titleInfo-compact</value>
            <local-name>relatedItem</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <help>
                <p> Role contains a description of the role of the person or institution named above to the resource being catalogued.</p>
                <p> Repeat for each new role played by the named entity, i.e. the same person or institution can have several roles in relation to one
                    resource.</p>
                <p> The more common roles are listed at the top.</p>
                <p> More role input options can be found on the Name Information tab on the Citation Forms.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>role-compact</value>
            <local-name>role</local-name>
            <parent>name</parent>
            <tab-id/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <help>
                <p>Role contains a coded and/or textual description of the role of the person, corporation or conference entered into Name Part to the resource
                    being catalogued. Repeat Role for each new role played by the the person, corporation or conference.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>role</value>
            <local-name>role</local-name>
            <parent>name</parent>
            <tab-id/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <help>
                <p>Role contains a coded and/or textual description of the role of the person, corporation or conference entered into Name Part to the resource
                    being catalogued. An authority should be indicated if using a coded form for role. </p>
                <p> Coded input is preselected as Type. The MARC Code List for Relators is preselected as Authority, with the most common roles placed at the
                    top. </p>
                <p> If both a coded term and a textual term are given that represent the same role, use one Role and two occurrences of Role Term.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>roleTerm</value>
            <local-name>roleTerm</local-name>
            <parent>role</parent>
            <tab-id/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <help>
                <p>Select a Role Term from the list. </p>
                <p> Note that "Author" is primarily used in connection with printed resources, whereas "Creator" is primarily used in connection with other
                    resources.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>roleTerm-code</value>
            <local-name>roleTerm</local-name>
            <parent>role</parent>
            <tab-id/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <help>
                <p>Select a term from the list. </p>
                <p> The list of terms given if "Text" is chosen for Type is the same as the list given if "Code" is chosen for Type and Authority is MARC Code
                    List for Relators. However, the values entered into the database are different. If Code is chosen, "aut" will e.g be input, whereas "Author"
                    will be input if "Text" is chosen. It is recomended to input each role in both coded and textual form. </p>
                <p> If "Text" is chosen, you can also input a term not on the list.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>roleTerm-text</value>
            <local-name>roleTerm</local-name>
            <parent>role</parent>
            <tab-id/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <help>
                <p>Type is used to express whether the Role Term has textual or coded form.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>roleTerm-type</value>
            <local-name>roleTerm</local-name>
            <parent>role</parent>
            <tab-id/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <help>
                <p>If the Type is in coded form, the authority file followed must be indicated.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>roleTerm-authority</value>
            <local-name>roleTerm</local-name>
            <parent>role</parent>
            <tab-id/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <help>
                <p> Use Script to record the script in which the name in rendered. </p>
                <p>Script can be applied the Name as a whole. Do this if you are using only one Script value for all Name Parts. If you are using different
                    values for different Name Parts, apply Script to each Name Part and leave Script empty under Name as a whole. </p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>name-script</value>
            <local-name>script</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <help>
                <p>Use Script to record the script in which the name in rendered. </p>
                <p> Script can be applied the Name as a whole. Do this if you are using only one Script value for all Name Parts. If you are using different
                    values for different Name Parts, apply Script to each Name Part and leave Script empty under Name as a whole.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>namePart-script</value>
            <local-name>script</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <help>
                <p> Script specifies the script used within individual fields. The use of Latin script is not noted. "Chinese" is "Han (Simplified Variant)" or
                    "Han (Traditional Variant)". If the two variants are not considered, it is "Han (Hanzi, Kanji, Hanja)", which is also used for Japanese,
                    Korean and Vietnamese written in Chinese. </p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>script</value>
            <local-name>script</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <help>
                <p> Script specifies the script used within individual fields. The use of Latin script is not noted. "Chinese" is "Han (Simplified Variant)" or
                    "Han (Traditional Variant)". If the two variants are not considered, it is "Han (Hanzi, Kanji, Hanja)", which is also used for Japanese,
                    Korean and Vietnamese written in Chinese. </p>
                <p>The script noted here is the script chosen when the record was created. It applies to the record as a whole, unless otherwise noted. Since a
                    title or a name as a subject can be in any script, the Global Script can be overruled here by chosing a Local Script.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>script-global-compact</value>
            <local-name>script</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <help>
                <p> Script specifies the script used within individual fields. The use of Latin script is not noted. "Chinese" is "Han (Simplified Variant)" or
                    "Han (Traditional Variant)". If the two variants are not considered, it is "Han (Hanzi, Kanji, Hanja)", which is also used for Japanese,
                    Korean and Vietnamese written in Chinese. </p>
                <p>The script noted here is not the script chosen when the record was created. the script noted here only applies to the field(s) immediately
                    below. Since a title or a name as a subject can be in any script, the Global Script can be overruled here by chosing a Local Script.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>script-local-compact</value>
            <local-name>script</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <help>
                <p> Script specifies the script used within individual fields. The use of Latin script is not noted. "Chinese" is "Han (Simplified Variant)" or
                    "Han (Traditional Variant)". If the two variants are not considered, it is "Han (Hanzi, Kanji, Hanja)", also used for Japanese, Korean and
                    Vietnamese written in Chinese. </p>
                <p>Note that the value shown here is the value chosen when the record template was chosen. This value applies to the whole record, not just to
                    the field above which it is noted. If you change the value, the change will apply to the whole record. </p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>script-compact</value>
            <local-name>script</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <help>
                <p> A subject is a term or a phrase that represents the primary topic(s) on which a work is focused. Use at least one subject field in each
                    record. Enter as many specific terms as necessary to capture the subject content. Be consistent in the formatting of subject terms. </p>
                <p> Values for subject indicate what content is found within or represented by the work, and typically answer such questions as who, what,
                    where, and when. </p>
                <p> While it is allowed to place multiple values in a single Topic string, it is the preferred practice to split up subject terms into separate
                    subfields, each of which answer the question of who, what, where, and when in relation to the resource being catalogued. </p>
                <p> A Subject is here basically composed of a Topic, a Place reference and a Time reference. All these fields are optional, that is, one can
                    have a Topic without any Place or Time reference, and one can have a Place reference without a Topic or a Time reference. To have a Time
                    reference all on its own would be a little unusual, but if period labels are used, this might still be acceptable.</p>
                <p>Topics can be divided into different kinds: "plain" Topics, Name topics and Work topics. "Plain" topics are references to abstract or
                    concrete entities that are not persons or organisations or works created by these. Topics of this kind are "beauty" or "bicycle",
                    "democracy" or "doors". No distinction is made between abstract or concrete topics. In addition to plain topics, a person or an institution
                    can serve as topic, examples being "George Washington" or "United Nations." These are treated like the names of authors and editors. If a
                    work of literature or art, or any other creation, serves as topic, it is treated as a title. These three subtypes address different aspects
                    of the "what" of a subject. </p>
                <p> The "where" of a subject can be expressed in a number of ways. "Place" simply contains the name of the place. </p>
                <p> "Time", the answer to "when," can be encoded in a number of different ways. The recommendation is to use the w3cdtf encoding. According to
                    this encoding, dates are formatted in the following way: Year: YYYY (e.g. 1997); Year and month: YYYY-MM (e.g. 1997-07); Complete date:
                    YYYY-MM-DD (e.g. 1997-07-16). </p>
                <p> Date ranges are indicated using "start" and "end" in Point. If a date range is open to one side, leave that side blank. If the date is
                    completely unknown, leave the Date field blank. </p>
                <p> In Time one can also use period designations, such as "the Middle Ages" and "Industrialisation," with the dangers of differing construals
                    that this implies. If you enter a time designation which uses a designaitn of this type, choose "text" in type.</p>
                <p> More input options can be accessed by clicking the Subjects tab on Context Description Forms.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>subject</value>
            <local-name>subject</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <help>
                <p> Subtitle is used to record a part of a title that is secondary to the core title. </p>
                <p> Use Subtitle whenever a subtitle is present, rather than including the subtitle in Title. </p>
                <p> When using Subtitle, do not include punctuation intended to separate the title from the subtitle at the end of Title. </p>
                <p> If more than two levels are in evidence in the whole title, i.e. if there is a sub-subtitle, include the sub-subtitle in Subtitle, with
                    appropriate punctuation. <!--NB: What are the rules here? Should not subTitle repeat?-->
                </p>
                <p> Subtitle contains every part of the title that do not belong in Non Sort, Title, Part Number or Part Name. </p>
            </help>
            <hint> Subtitle is used to record a part of a title that is secondary to the core title. </hint>
            <value>subTitle</value>
            <local-name>subTitle</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <help>
                <p> Subtitle is used to record a part of a title that is secondary to the core title. </p>
                <p> Use Subtitle whenever a subtitle is present, rather than including the subtitle in Title. </p>
                <p> Subtitle contains every part of the title that do not belong in Non Sort, Title, Part Number or Part Name. </p>
            </help>
            <hint> Subtitle is used to record a part of a title that is secondary to the core title. </hint>
            <value>subTitle-compact</value>
            <local-name>subTitle</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <help/>
            <hint/>
            <value>titleInfo-supplied</value>
            <local-name>supplied</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <help>
                <p> Use Time for chronological subject terms or temporal coverage. Time may be expressed as a subject term (e.g. "Middle Ages") or as a
                    structured date (e.g. "2001-09-11"). In the first case, choose "text" in Type; otherwise choose "YYY-MM-DD" and enter the time you wish to
                    refer to as precisely as possible.</p>
                <p> Point is used to note whether the date noted is a start point or an end point when using a structured date. If no point is specified, date
                    is assumed to be a single date. </p>
                <p> More input options can be accessed by clicking the Subjects tab on Context Description Forms.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>temporal</value>
            <local-name>temporal</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <help>
                <p> Title contains the core title of the resource catalogued. </p>
                <p> At least one Title is required. When no title appears on the item being described, a title should be supplied. </p>
                <p> Title includes all parts of a title that are not covered by Non Sort, Subtitle, Part Number and Part Name. </p>
                <p> Dates may be recorded under Title or Subtitle only if they are part of the title. Publication dates are included under Origin Information. </p>
                <p> For parallel titles, i.e., equivalent titles in different languages that have not been translated by the cataloguer, add a Title Information
                    and enter the Title there with the Type "Alternative" for each parallel title. Note the language, script and transliteration of each title. </p>
                <p> For a title translated or transcribed by the cataloguer, add a Title Information and enter the Title there with the Type "Translated" or
                    "Transliterated" for each title. Note the language, script and transliteration of each title added in this way. </p>
                <p> For abbreviated titles, add a Title Information block and enter the Title there with the Type "Abbreviated" for each parallel title. </p>
                <p> For uniform titles, i.e., titles with various renderings that are unified by an authority file, add a Title Information and enter the Title
                    there with the Type "Uniform". Under each uniform title, state the Authority according to which the uniform title has been selected. </p>
            </help>
            <hint>Title contains the core title of the resource catalogued. Title includes all parts of a title that are not covered by Non Sort, Subtitle, Part
                Number and Part Name. A Title is required: when no title appears on the item being described, a title should be supplied. </hint>
            <value>title</value>
            <local-name>title</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <help>
                <p> Title contains the core title of the resource catalogued. </p>
                <p> At least one Title is required. When no title appears on the item being described, a title should be supplied. </p>
                <p> Title includes all parts of a title that are not covered by Non Sort, Subtitle, Part Number and Part Name. </p>
            </help>
            <hint>Title contains the core title of the resource catalogued. Title includes all parts of a title that are not covered by Non Sort, Subtitle, Part
                Number and Part Name. A Title is required: when no title appears on the item being described, a title should be supplied. </hint>
            <value>title-compact</value>
            <local-name>title</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <help>
                <p> Enter here the title of the book or the work of art that serves as topic for the resource you are cataloguing. If the title divides into a
                    main title and a subtitle, enter each part in its separate field. If the subtitle divides into several parts, separate the parts with a
                    semicolon. </p>
                <p> More input options can be accessed by clicking the Subjects tab on Context Description Forms.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>subject-titleInfo</value>
            <local-name>titleInfo</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <help>
                <p> At least one Title inside a Title Information is required. Title Information can be repeated for alternative, translated, transliterated or
                    uniform titles. These values are chosen in Type. For the basic Title Information entry, leave Type blank or use the value "Basic Title
                    Information". If, in addition to the basic title, you also wish to record an alternative, translated, transliterated or uniform title, add a
                    Title Information and choose the relevant Type. Repeat Title Information as many times as necessary. </p>
                <p> A Title Information consists of a main Title, plus a number of supplementary fields that relate to it. A Title may have a Subtitle, usually
                    an expansion of the Title proper. If the Title begins with a word according to which it should not be sorted (such as "The" or "A" and the
                    like), enter this word in Non Sort and remove it from Title. If a publication consists of several parts, parts that are either numbered or
                    named, use Part Number and/or Part Name. "A History of Philosophy" may have several numbered parts, such as "Part One. Ancient Greek
                    Philosophy." Enter "Part One" in Part Number and "Ancient Greek Philosophy" in Part Name. </p>
                <p> When no title appears on the item being described, a title should be supplied. Use Display Label to indicate that the title is supplied, by
                    giving it the value "Supplied Title". A supplied title should be created in accordance with an established standard and describe, as
                    concisely as possible, the content of the resource in question. If no standards apply, consider carefully the expectations users have for
                    the naming of similar resources. </p>
                <p> If an alternative, translated or transliterated title is recorded, choose the relevant Type for each separate Title Information. </p>
                <p> If a uniform or an abbreviated title is recorded, choose the appropriate value in Type and note in which authority file the uniform or
                    abbreviated title in Authority has been found. Authority files are only used in connection with uniform and abbreviated titles. </p>
                <p> Record the language of the Title Information by choosing the language used in the resource, if this is different from the language noted in
                    Language of Resource, a field describing the language of the resource as a whole. The Language of Resource was selected when opening the
                    editor; it may be modified in the Resource Languages tab.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>titleInfo</value>
            <local-name>titleInfo</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <help>
                <p> Enter here the title of the book, article or anthology contribution you are cataloguing. If the title divides into a main title and a
                    subtitle, enter each part in its separate field. If the subtitle divides into several parts, separate the parts with a semicolon. </p>
                <p> If the title is in a language that is usually transliterated, enter the transliterated title and subtitle in their respective fields. Use
                    the transliteration scheme you chose when selecting a record template.</p>
                <p> If you believe it is useful to supply a translation of the title, do so in the relevant fields. Note the language that the title information
                    is translated into (the default is English). </p>
                <p> More input options can be found on the Title Info tab on the Citation Forms.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>titleInfo-compact</value>
            <local-name>titleInfo</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <help>
                <p> Type identifies what type of Title Information is recorded, if this information is special. If the title is recorded as it appears on the
                    title page, it does not have Type. Use Type if the title is abbreviated, translated, alternative, or uniform (a transliteration is here
                    regarded as a form of translation). </p>
                <p> When an abbreviated title is present, an Authority must be chosen. An alternative title may be a parallel title found in the authoritative
                    title information (in written works, typically the title page) or a title that does not occur in the authoritative title information, e.g. a
                    title found on a cover. If the alternative title does not occur in the authoritative title information, indicate in Display Label where the
                    information comes from (e.g., "Cover Title"). If the alternative title occurs in the authoritative title information, it can e.g. be a
                    translation or a transliteration of the main title information. If a translated or a transliterated title occurs in the authoritative title
                    information of the work being catalogued, choose "Alternative" for Type and note the language, transliteration and script of the title
                    information, as appropriate, if this is different from the language noted in Language of Resource. If this is not the case and you have e.g.
                    supplied the translation or transliteration yourself, choose "Translated" for Type and note the language, transliteration and script of the
                    title information, as appropriate. </p>
                <p> A uniform title is a title that refers uniformly to a work that is known by several titles, e.g. the works of Shakespeare or the Bible. When
                    a uniform title is present, an Authority for its selection must be chosen. </p>
            </help>
            <hint> Type identifies what type of Title Information is recorded, if this information is special. If the title is recorded as it appears on the
                title page, it does not have Type and Type should be left empty. Use a value for Type if the title is abbreviated, translated, alternative, or
                uniform (a transliteration is here regarded as a form of translation). </hint>
            <value>titleInfo-type</value>
            <local-name>titleInfo</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <help>
                <p> Enter here the title of the edited volume you are cataloguing. If the title divides into a main title and a subtitle, enter each part in its
                    separate field. </p>
                <p> If the title is in a language that is usually transliterated, enter the transliterated title and subtitle in their respective fields. Use
                    the transliteration scheme you chose when selecting a record template. </p>
                <p> If you believe it is useful to supply a translation of the title, do so in their relevant fields. Note the language that the title
                    information is translated into (the default is English). </p>
                <p> The language used is only specified if it is different from the language noted in Language of Resource when you selected the record
                    template. The most common languages have been moved to the top of the list. </p>
            </help>
            <value>edited-volume-titleInfo-compact</value>
            <local-name>titleInfo</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <help>
                <p> Use Topic to indicate any primary subjects that do not fit into the Place, Time, Works as Topics, or Persons and Institutions as Topics
                    subfields. In general, abstract nouns should be used. Add as many Topic fields as you need in order to analyse your topic. The relation
                    between the different fields is not specified, but one may start with more abstract terms and move to more specific terms, within the same
                    Subject.</p>
                <p> More input options can be accessed by clicking the Subjects tab on Context Description Forms.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>topic</value>
            <local-name>topic</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <help>
                <p> This field specifies the transliteration (transcription, romanisation) scheme used within Name Information. When specificing the
                    transliteration used, also specify the language employed. There is at present no standard list of transliteration schemes available. If you
                    wish to employ a transliteration on the scheme, please contact <!--contact -->. In general, the Library of Congress transliteration schemes
                    (<!-- NB -->) should be used. If you follow a transliteration scheme authorised by <!--NB-->, choose <!--NB--> as the value and note the
                    language from which the transliteration is made. The following transliteration schemes are authorised by <!--NB-->: Chinese: pinyin
                    Japanese: (modified) Hepburn Korean: <!--NB--> Russian: <!--NB--> Sanskrit: <!--NB--> If you employ a different, but recognised,
                    transliteration scheme, you may have it added to the list. </p>
            </help>
            <hint>Transliteration specifies the transliteration (transcription, romanisation) scheme used within Title Information. When specificing the
                transliteration used, also specify the language employed. </hint>
            <value>name-transliteration</value>
            <local-name>transliteration</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <help>
                <p>This field specifies the transliteration (transcription, romanisation) scheme used within Title Information. When specificing the
                    transliteration used, also specify the language employed. There is at present no standard list of transliteration schemes available. If you
                    wish to employ a transliteration on the scheme, please contact <!--contact -->. In general, the Library of Congress transliteration schemes
                    (<!-- NB -->) should be used. If you follow a transliteration scheme authorised by <!--NB-->, choose <!--NB--> as the value and note the
                    language from which the transliteration is made. The following transliteration schemes are authorised by <!--NB-->: Chinese: pinyin
                    Japanese: (modified) Hepburn Korean: <!--NB--> Russian: <!--NB--> Sanskrit: <!--NB--> If you employ a different, but recognised,
                    transliteration scheme, you may have it added to the list. </p>
                <p> Script can be applied the Name as a whole. Do this if you are using only one Script value for all Name Parts. If you are using different
                    values for different Name Parts, apply Script to each Name Part and leave Script empty under Name as a whole.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>namePart-transliteration</value>
            <local-name>transliteration</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <help>
                <p> Transliteration specifies the transliteration (transcription, romanisation) scheme used within Title Information. When specificing the
                    transliteration used, also specify the language employed. There is at present no standard list of transliteration schemes available. If you
                    wish to employ a transliteration on the scheme, please contact <!--contact -->. In general, the Library of Congress transliteration schemes
                    (<!-- NB -->) should be used. If you follow a transliteration scheme authorised by <!--NB-->, choose <!--NB--> as the value and note the
                    language from which the transliteration is made. The following transliteration schemes are authorised by <!--NB-->: Chinese: pinyin
                    Japanese: (modified) Hepburn Korean: <!--NB--> Russian: <!--NB--> Sanskrit: <!--NB--> If you employ a different, but recognised,
                    transliteration scheme, you may have it added to the list. </p>
            </help>
            <hint>Transliteration specifies the transliteration (transcription, romanisation) scheme used within Title Information. When specificing the
                transliteration used, also specify the language employed. </hint>
            <value>titleInfo-transliteration</value>
            <local-name>transliteration</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <help>
                <p> Transliteration specifies the transliteration (transcription, romanisation) scheme used.</p>
                <p>Note that the value shown here is the value chosen when the record template was chosen. This value applies to the whole record, not just to
                    the field above which it is noted. If you change the value, the change will apply to the whole record. </p>
            </help>
            <hint>Transliteration specifies the transliteration (transcription, romanisation) scheme used within Title Information. When specificing the
                transliteration used, also specify the language employed. </hint>
            <value>transliteration-compact</value>
            <local-name>transliteration</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <help>
                <p> Transliteration specifies the transliteration (transcription, romanisation) scheme used.</p>
                <p>Note that the value shown here is the value chosen when the record template was chosen. This value applies to the whole record, not just to
                    the field above which it is noted. If you change the value, the change will apply to the whole record. </p>
                <p>The transliteration noted here is the transliteration chosen when the record was created. It applies to the record as a whole, unless
                    otherwise noted. Since a title or a name as a subject can be in any transliteration, the Global Transliteration can be overruled here by
                    chosing a Local Transliteration .</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>transliteration-global-compact</value>
            <local-name>transliteration</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <help>
                <p> Transliteration specifies the transliteration (transcription, romanisation) scheme used.</p>
                <p>Note that the value shown here is the value chosen when the record template was chosen. This value applies to the whole record, not just to
                    the field above which it is noted. If you change the value, the change will apply to the whole record. </p>
                <p>The transliteration noted here is not the transliteration chosen when the record was created. The transliteration noted here only applies to
                    the field(s) immediately below. Since a title or a name as a subject can be in any language , the Global Transliteration can be overruled
                    here by chosing a Local Transliteration.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>transliteration-local-compact</value>
            <local-name>transliteration</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <help>
                <p> In URL, record the Uniform Resource Locator (URL) of a resource accessed on the Internet.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>url-compact</value>
            <local-name>url</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <help>
                <p>Usage with the value "primary" can be used with repeated fields to indicate special prominence of one that is useful for various special
                    purposes such as indexing.</p>
                <p>When applied to Name, "primary" indicates the name that would probably be used when citing the resource. This is useful when there are
                    several authors and for citation purposes one is to be selected. The "primary" name would be used with the resource title for the citation,
                    and also would be the name that would be associated with the uniform title when one is present.</p>
            </help>
            <hint>Usage with the value "primary" can be used with repeated fields to indicate special prominence of one that is useful for various special
                purposes such as indexing. </hint>
            <value>name-usage</value>
            <local-name>usage</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <help>
                <p>Usage with the value "primary" can be used with repeated fields to indicate special prominence of one that is useful for various special
                    purposes such as indexing.</p>
            </help>
            <hint>Usage with the value "primary" can be used with repeated fields to indicate special prominence of one that is useful for various special
                purposes such as indexing. </hint>
            <value>usage</value>
            <local-name>usage</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <help/>
            <hint/>
            <value>name-value-uri</value>
            <local-name>valueUri</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <help/>
            <hint/>
            <value>titleInfo-valueURI</value>
            <local-name>valueURI</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <help>
                <p> XLink is used to reference an external resource, such as a second metadata record, a Related Item or a Table of Contents. </p>
            </help>
            <hint> XLink is used to reference an external resource, such as a metadata record, a Related Item or a Table of Contents. </hint>
            <value>xlink:href</value>
            <local-name>xlink:href</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <help>
                <p> The language used within Title Information is specified here, if this language is different from the language noted in Language of Resource.
                    xml:lang is used to specify the language used within a field, using specifications in RFC 3066. RFC 3066 uses the two-character ISO 639-1
                    codes along with three-character ISO 639-2 codes for those languages not given in 639-1. </p>
                <p> The recommendation is not to use xml:lang, but to use Language. </p>
            </help>
            <hint>The language used within Title Information is specified here, if this language is different from the language noted in Language of Resource.
                The recommendation is not to use xml:lang, but to use Language. </hint>
            <value>xml:lang</value>
            <local-name>xml:lang</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id/>
        </item>
    </items>
</code-table><!--return
for $item in $code-table/items/item
order by upper-case($item/value)
return $item-->