<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<div>
    <h4>Search syntax</h4>
    <p>In Tamboti, when one searches for a specific term, only matches with the full term are
        retrieved, that is, a search for "Chin" does not retrieve all words beginning with "Chin"
        ("China", "Chinese" …), but only "Chin".</p>
    <p>One can use <em>wildcards</em> to perform broader searches. "?" can be used for a single
        character and "*" for zero, one or more characters: "China" is thus found with "Ch?na" and
        "C*a", and "China" and "Chine" are found with "Chin?", just as "China", "Chine" and
        "Chinese" are found with "Chin*". Note that "*" and "?" (unfortunately) cannot occur in the
        beginning of a word.</p>
    <p>
        <em>Fuzzy searches</em> can be performed by putting "~" at the end of a word, make it
        possible to retrieve "Chine" through "China~". One can quantify the fuzziness, by appending
        a number between 0.0 and 1.0, "complete fuzziness" (finding everything) being 0.0 and
        complete identity being "1.0". If you append a "~" with no number, you use the value 0.5.
        (Note that the actual value "1.0" is illegal: use "0.999…" instead.)</p>
    <p>
        <em>Phrases </em>can be searched for by putting them in quotation marks. Use "straight"
        double quotation marks only, that is, not single quotations marks or double quotation marks
        that are curly.</p>
    <p>If one searches for ""Reform and Progress"", putting the two words in quotation marks, one
        will only find records in which the three words occurs in sequence, not if they occurs in a
        different sequence (e.g. "Progress and Reform") or at different points in the record, 
        one word occurring in the title, another in a note and the third in the name of the publisher.</p>
    <p>Note that Chinese, Japanese and Korean characters are indexed as separate words, so a search
        for "本日" (without quotation marks) will find records with the two characters in the opposite
        sequence, that is, with "日本" as well. However, if you enclose "日本" in quotation marks, you
        only retrieve records with the two characters in the specified sequence.</p>
    <p>The <em>boolean operators</em> "AND" and "OR" can be used. If you search for "China AND
        Japan", you will find only records with both the words. If you search for "China OR Japan",
        you will find records in which either or both the two words occur. The first search will
        normally result in fewer records than the second search. "NOT" can also be used. If you
        search for "China NOT Japan", you will only find records that have "China" but not "Japan".
        This search would also normally result in fewer records.</p>
    <p>You can also make boolean searches using Advanced Search.</p>
    <p>One can make even more complicated searches by using parentheses: "(China OR Japan) NOT
        Korea" will thus find records in which the words "China" or "Japan" occur, but only those in
        which "Korea" does not occur.</p>
    <p>One must write "AND", "OR" and "NOT" in uppercase letters. Otherwise, searches are made in
        lower-case letters only, so writing "China" with initial lower-case "C" (as "china") has the exact same
        effect as using an initial upper-case "C". </p>
</div>